A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- One East 75th Street, 1907-1985; 1
  - Facility and Operations, 1.2
    - Plumbing
      - 3/22/1907, 1362 (Folder 16)
        Detail of Sump Caisson, Section on Line "A-A", Section on Line "B-B", Plan at Pump Level, Plan at Motor Level, # 1-18"x15 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-14 5/8"x18", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-14 3/4"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-16 1/4"x18 3/4", Paper (black ink), # 5-Written on the Back in Pen, Sump Caisson, Laundry Plan 1908, 14 7/8"x18", Linen, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
      - 3/29/1907, Part of 1362 (Folder 16)
        Detail of Upper Corner Tank, # 1-16 1/8"x7 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # # 1-No, # 2-No 2-16 3/4"x7 3/4", Photocopy Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
      - 4/15/1907, 1372A (Folder 17)
        Plumbing Plans, Section Looking South, Section Looking North, Section Looking West, (In two pieces) # 1-34 3/4"x27 3/4", # 2-4 1/4"x6 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
      - 12/2/1907, 1453 (Folder 17)
        Revised Detail of Sump Caisson, Elevation, Plan, Section "A-A", # 1-18 3/8"x22 1/8", Linen, # 2-18 1/2"x22", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
      - 12/5/1907, 1454 (Folder 17)
        Sketch of Proposed Ground Water Well in Cellar, Section "A-A, Plan "A", 36"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
    - Electrical
      - 8/31/1908, 18/3 (Folder 18)
        Extension Pushes, Full Size, 10 7/8"x7 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Lord Electric Company
      - 5/19/1908, Order Number 2047, 1824/9 (Folder 18)
        Meter Board, Iron Lined Wood Box, 29"x@23 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
      - 3/11/1908, Revised 3/?/1908; 4/18/1908; Order Number 3168, 1824/6 (Folder 18)
        Interconnection Boxes, Iron Lined Wood Boxes For All Floors, # 1-21"x18 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-21 3/4"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
      - 4/10/1908, No Number Listed (Area is Torn and Missing) (rolled with Order Number 2047) (Folder 18)
        Meter Board, Iron Lined Wood Boxes, 27 3/4"x19, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N.A., (H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.)
      - undated, No Number Listed (Torn Off) (Folder 18)
        No Title (Torn Off) (Pull Box), 33 5/8"x@23 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
- Cellar/Basement, 1906-1991; 2
  - Building/Floor Plans, 2.1
    - 4/29/1907, Revised 2/4/1908; 102 NY 33 (Folder 19-20)
      Cellar Plan, Basement Plan, # 1-White Paper Attached (Taped), 10/64, Measurements (in Red Ink), 41 3/4"x32 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, White Paper-4 7/8"x3", # 2-41 7/8"x32 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-41 1/2"x32 1/8", Paper (Blue Ink), # 4-20 7/8"x16 3/4", Paper (Photocopier Paper), # 5-41 7/8"x32 1/4", Linen, # 6-Paper Size-42 1/4"x32 3/8", Polyester Paper, # 7-42 1/4"x32 3/8", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 12/28/1950-2/2/1953, Job Number 421, Drawing Number 1 (Folder 21-22)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      #2-Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #3-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler
      Alteration to One East 75th St N.Y.C. for the Commonwealth Fund, Cellar Floor Plan, Sub Cellar Floor Plan, Lighting Riser Diagram, Schedule for Distribution Panel, Notes, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Telephone, 42"x26 1/4", Diazo Blue Print: 4/10/1951-General Owner Requests-DV Removed, 4/23/1951-Plumbing and General Notes Added, 5/16/1951-Owner Requests, 5/22/1951-Equipment Note Changed, Drink Fountain Added, Rm C-11, Case Retained Rm C-11, # 2-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Paper, # 3-Has the Architects Pencil Notations, 42 1/4"x26 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-No Electrical Stamp, 41 3/4"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 5-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print.
      #1-12/28/1950 #2-Revised 6/26/1951 #3-Revised 6/26/1951 #4-Revised 4/10/1951 #5-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 Rogers and Butler
    - 6/26/1951-2/2/1953, 87 (Folder 21-22)
      Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler.
      # 6-Electrical (Stamped), 42 7/8"x26 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Small Drawing/Note Attached-Basement Elevator Foyer, 4"x6", Paper # 7-Electrical, Revisions: 6/1951-Outlets and New Fixtures Added and Omitted in Space Nos C-6, C-11, Exhaust Fan in Rm C-4 by Elec Contractor, 2/1953-Revised as per Contractors Marked Up Drawings, 43 1/2"x27 3/4", Linen (Blue), Architects, # 1-Rogers and Butler, # 2-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 3-4-Rogers and Butler, # 5-7-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers.
      #6-Revised 6/26/1951 #7-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953
    - undated, No Number Listed (Rolled with 301 NY 1-4 {Trunk Room}) (Folder 23)
      Cellar Plan, West Elevation, South Elevation, North Elevation, 26"x19 1/8", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A, Probably James Gamble Rogers
    - undated, No Number Listed (Rolled with 301 NY 1-4 {Trunk Room}) (Folder 23)
      Cellar Plan {Much of the drawing was done free hand-includes labels and measurements}, 24 3/8"x19 1/8", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A, Probably James Gamble Rogers
    - Coal Vault
      - 2/3/1914, 1205 (Office Copy), Order Number 1903, Drawing Number 1631 (Folder 24)
        Chute, Coal and Wood Bins, (3 drawings taped together before filming), Door to Large Coal Bunker, Plan, Section A-A, Section B-B, Section C-C, Section D-D, Section E-E, Section H, 34"x35 1/2", Diazo Blueprint, Architects, Levering and Garrigues Co.
    - Boiler Room
      - 10/29/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 25)
        Sketch Showing Location Boiler Foundation, Plan, Section, Written on the Back in Pencil, Sketch Showing Location of Boiler Foundations, 19 7/8"x14 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, G.A. Suter and Co.
    - Trunk Room
      - undated, 101 NY No 1 (Folder 26)
        Trunk Room Arrangements, Cellar Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, 28"x17 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 101 NY No 2 (Folder 26)
      - undated, 101 NY No 3 (Folder 26)
        Trunk Room Arrangements, Cellar Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, 28 1/4"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 101 NY No 4 (Folder 26)
        Trunk Room Arrangements, Cellar Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, 28"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 301 NY No. 1 (Folder 26)
        Elevation of Trunk Room Arrangement, South Elevation (Mrs. Harkness), End Elevation, West Elevation (Mr. H and Miss Coleman), North Elevation (Silver Chests), 28 1/2"x17 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 301 NY No. 2 (Folder 26)
        Elevation of Trunk Room Arrangement, South Elevation (Mrs. Harkness), End Elevation, West Elevation (Mr. H and Miss Coleman), North Elevation (Silver Chests), 28 3/8"x17 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 301 NY No. 3 and 4 (Folder 26)
        Elevation of Trunk Room Arrangement, South Elevation (Mrs. Harkness), West Elevation (Mr. H and Miss Coleman), North Elevation (Silver Chests), 28 1/2"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 501 NY No 1 (Folder 27)
        3/4 Inch Scale and Full Size Details of Trunk Racks, Full Size-Section, Plans-Corners, Divisions, Plan of Upper Tiers, Plan of Bottom Tier, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section, Plan of Silver Chest Platform, 28 3/8"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 501 NY No 2 (Folder 27)
        3/4 Inch Scale and Full Size Details of Trunk Racks, Full Size Details, Plan, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section, 28 1/4"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 501 NY No 3 (Folder 27)
        3/4 Inch Scale and Full Size Details of Trunk Racks, Full Size Details, Plan, Section Showing Slats, Section Showing Division, Plan, Section Showing Ends, 28 1/4"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
      - undated, 501 NY No 4 (Folder 27)
        3/4 Inch Scale and Full Size Details of Trunk Racks, Full Size Details, Plan, Section Showing Floors, Section Showing Division, Plan, Section Showing Ends, 28 1/4"x17 7/8", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
  - Building/Floor Plans, 2.2
    - 11/8/1906, 1 NY 33 (Folder 28)
      Basement Floor Plan, 42"x22", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - undated (1991), 101 (Folder 29)
      Demolition Plan (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/2"x18 1/4", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - undated (1991), 102 (Folder 29)
      Construction Plan (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/2"x18 1/8", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - 4/29/1907, 109 NY33 (Folder 28)
      Basement Floor and First Floor Framing Plan, Section "A-A", "B-B", "C-C", "D-D", Section Thro' Elevator Pit, Elevator Pit Framing, Section at Entrance Looking North, Section Through Top of Kitchen Window, Notes on the Right Side, (2 Copies) # 1-42"x32 1/4", Linen, # 2-42"x32 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - undated (1991), 201 (Folder 29)
      Elevation, A-North Elevation, B-South Elevation (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/4"x18", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - undated (1991), 202 (Folder 29)
      Elevations, A-East Elevation, B-West Elevation, C-Cornice Section (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/4"x18 1/4", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - undated (1991), 301 (Folder 29)
      Panel Details A-Wall Panel Section (Full Scale), B-Cabinet Section (Full Scale), C-Upper Panel Section (Full Scale) (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/4"x18 1/4", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - 8/13/1985, A1 (Folder 30-31)
      Construction and Ceiling Plans, # 1-36 1/4"x24 1/8", Sepia Tone, # 2-36 1/4"x24 1/8", Sepia Tone (Copy of # 1), # 3-36"x24", Vellum, # 4-36 1/2"x24 1/8", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 5-36 1/2"x24 1/8", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 6-36 1/4"x24 1/4", Paper (Tan Paper and Blue Ink), Stamped for Permit Approval by N.Y.C. Department of Buildings, 10/1/1985, No Reflective Ceiling Plan on this Copy, # 7-36 1/4"x24 1/4", Paper (Tan Paper and Blue Ink), Stamped for Permit Approval by N.Y.C. Department of Buildings, 10/1/1985, No Reflective Ceiling Plan on this Copy, Architects, Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch
    - 8/13/1985, A3 (Folder 32)
      Elevations, A-Section (Br 1 and 2, K, BA1), 1-Elevation, Kitchen, B-Section, C-Section (Br 1-3, CL, Bath 2), D-Section (Entry Hall, LR, Br 1 and 3, CL), E-Section (Living Room), F-Section (Bath 2, Entry Hall, Br Hall, Br 3), 2-Elevation (Mail Storage Room), 3-Elevation, G-Section (Mail Room), H-Section (Mail Room), l-Section (Br 1-3),, # 1-36 1/4"x24", Sepia Tone, # 2-36 1/4"x24 1/4", Sepia Tone (Copy of # 1), # 3-36"x24", Vellum, # 4-36 1/4"x24 1/2", paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 5-36 1/2"x24 1/8", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 6-36 1/2"x24 1/8", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), Architects, Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch
    - 1981 March 20, A4 (Folder 33)
      Details, 1-Hall Elevation, 2-Hall Chair Rail, 3-Door Frame, 4-Bath 2, Floor, 5-Bath 2, Elevation, 6-Bedroom 1, Closet, 7-Closet Details, 8-Detail, 9-New AC Case/Existing AC Enclosure, 10 and 11-Detail, 12-Kitchen Liplight, 13-Kitchen Draws, # 1-36 1/4"x24", Sepia Tone, # 2-36 1/4"x24 1/8", Sepia Tone (Copy of # 1), # 3-36"x24", Vellum, # 4-36 1/2"x24 1/2", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 5-36 1/2"x24 1/4", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 6-36 1/2"x24 1/4", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), Architects, Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch
    - 6/26/1985, No Number Listed (Folder 34)
      Existing Plan, Basement, 35 7/8"x24", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A, (Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch)
    - 4/10/1986, No Number Listed (Folder 34)
      Basement Floor Plan, Site Plan, 36 1/8"x24", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A, (Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch)
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 34)
      A-North Elevation, B-East Elevation, C-South Elevation, D-West Elevation, (Renovations), 33 7/8"x22 1/8", Paper, Architects, N/A
    - Toilets
      - 11/14/1907, 311 NY 33 (Folder 35)
        Detail of Toilet Rooms in Basement and Cellar, Also Coal and Wood Bins and Wine Rack, 43 1/2"x20 1/4", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Pantry/Kitchen
      - undated, 0-2 (Folder 36)
        Special Storage Refrigerator, Plan, Section, Elevation of Door A and B, 26 1/4"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
        Received 6/19/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - undated, 0-3 (Folder 36)
        Special Kitchen and Pantry Refrigerator, 26 3/8"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
      - undated (6/19/1908), No Number Listed (Rolled with 02-04) (Folder 36)
        Small Drawing that was with Drawings 02-04 (Kitchen/Pantry), Wall Measurements and Window, 8"x5", Paper, N/A
      - 7/29/1907, 202 NY 33 (Folder 36)
        Section Through Lintel of East Window in Kitchen, 15 1/2"x10 1/4", Tan Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 11/9/1907, 309 NY 33 (Folder 37)
        Scale Details of Cases, Etc., in Basement Excepting Kitchen and Pantry, Dresser in Servants Dining Room, Section A-A, B-B, C-C, D-D, E-E, F-F, Elevation of Dresser and Sink in Servant Pantry, Section Through Closet in Man's Room, Others to be Similar, Elevations, Full Size Section Through Plate Rail, Plan (s), Elevation of Lockers in Servants Dining Room, Elevation of Dresser in Corridor, 41 3/4"x28", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 12/17/1907, 315 NY 33 (Folder 36)
        Kitchen, 23 1/2"x18 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1907, 399 NY 33 (Second Copy Doesn't Have Drawing Number-Torn Off) (Folder 37)
        Kitchen and Pantry Details, Plan of South Side of Kitchen, West Side of Pantry, Elevation of South Side of Kitchen, Elevation of West Side of Pantry, Case "X" in Pantry, Section "A-A" and "B-B" (Full Size), Section "C-C" (Scale), # 1, 1-45 1/8"x28", Linen, # 2-45 1/2"x28", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 990 (Office Copy) and0 - Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 36)
        #1-Received 6/5/1908 Charles T. Wills, 6/6/1908 Hale and Rogers #2-Received 5/25/1908 Charles T. Wills, 6/19/1908 Hale and Rogers
        Full Size Detail of Insulation of General Storage Refrigerator, # 1-26 3/8"x19 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-26 3/8"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
      - undated, 991 (Office Copy) (Folder 38)
        #1-Received 6/5/1908 Charles T. Wills, 6/6/1908 Haleand Rogers
        Special Storage Refrigerator, Plan, Elevation of Door A and B, Section, 26 3/8"x19 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
      - undated, 992 (Office Copy (Folder 38)
        Special Kitchen and Pantry Refrigerator, Elevation C, D, Section A and B, Horizontal Section Through Ice Chamber, 26 3/8"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
        #1-Received 6/5/1908 Charles T. Wills, 6/6/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - undated, P-37, 787 (Folder 38)
        Plan of Kitchen-Pantry Basement, Written on the Back in Pencil, Pottier and Stymus's Drawings of Kitchen Pantry in Basement, 20 3/8"x17", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
        Received 4/13/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - undated, P-38, 786 (Folder 38)
        West, Side of Kitchen-Pantry, Basement, 18 3/4"x17", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
        Received 4/13/1908 Charles T. Wills, 4/15/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - undated, P-39, 785 (Folder 38)
        North, Side of Kitchen-Pantry, Basement, 20 1/4"x16 5/8", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - 1981 April 3, No Number Listed (Folder 37)
        Basement Kitchen, (Commonwealth Fund), 36 3/8"x24", Vellum, Architects, N/A, (Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch)
    - Service Staircase
      - 5/19/1907, 133, Contract Number 1199 (Folder 39)
        No Title (Plans of a Spiral Staircase) -Plan at Landing, Plan at Start, 23 1/4"x8 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, - Elevation at "A-A", 23 1/4"x9", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Levering and Garrigues Co.
      - 12/12/1907, 312 NY 33 (Folder 40)
        Scale Details of Service Stair, Plan at Third Story, Plan at Mezzanine, Plan at Second Story, Plan at Platform Between First and Second Floors, Plan at First Story, Plan at Basement, Section of Stair from Cellar to Third Story, Plan of Stair from Front Hall to Gentlemen's Dressing Room, Section of Stairs from Third Story to the Attic, Section A-A, 38 7/8"x57 1/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 4/8/1908, 793 (Office Copy) - Second Copy Doesn't Have Office # (Folder 39)
        Measurements for Service Stair, Section "A-A" Looking South, Section at "B-B" Looking North, Section "C-C", # 1-21 1/4"x32 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Measurements for Stairs From 5th Fl to Attic, J. Williams-Detail, 21 1/8"x32 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
        #1-Received 3/29/1908 Charles T. Wills, 3/31/1908 Hale and Rogers #2-Received 4/10/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - 10/17/1908, 1198 (Office Copy) (Folder 39)
        Revised 3" Scale Plan of Stairs Under Main Elevator, 23"x28 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
  - HVAC, 2.3
    - 10/5/1982, C-1, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 41)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, Cellar Plan, 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - 5/24/1983, M-1 (Folder 42)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Demolition Cellar Floor Plan, HVAC Construction Cellar Floor Plan-HVAC-Notes on the Left Side, 49 1/4"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects-Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 5/24/1983, M-2 (Folder 42)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Demolition and Construction-Cellar Floor Plan-Piping, HVAC and Electric, Basement Floor Plan, Notes on the Right Side, 49"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 5/24/1983, M-8 (Folder 42)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Details, Supply Air Riser Diagram, Air Flow Schematic Basement Air Handler, Notes, Air Flow Schematic Attic Air Handler, Section "A-A"-Attic Air Handler, Section "B-B"-Attic Air Handler, Water Flow Schematic, Detail of Compression Tank, Detail Basement or Attic Chilled Water Coil Connection, Detail of VAV Box Connection, Valve Mode of Operation, 49 1/2"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 5/24/1983, M-9 (Folder 42)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Details-Detail for Thermostat Plate Elevation and End View, Detail of Base Removals for Piping Installations, New Suspension for Fifth Floor Ceiling for New Duct Work, Elevation of Typical Fan Coil Installation-Third Floor, Plan-Sectional Elevation of Section Through 12"x60" Duct Riser, Window and Louver Plan, Basement Air Duct Enclosure Elevation, 50"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 41)
      Cellar Plan, Section Showing Air Filters, Tempering Coils, Etc., Detail of Heating Stacks, Details of Air Filters, Plan of Air Filters, Elevation, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/4"x12 5/8", Paper, Architects, N/A
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 41)
      Basement Story Plan, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/4"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 2.4
    - 4/15/1907, 1364 (Folder 43)
      Plumbing Plans, Cellar Plan, 35 3/4"x27 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
    - 4/15/1907, 1365 (Folder 43)
      Plumbing Plans, Basement Plan, # 1-36 1/4"x18 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20 1/4"x10 1/4", Paper, Architects, Albert L Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 2.5
    - undated (1991), 103 (Folder 44)
      Electric Plan, Electric Symbols, Electric Notes (Staff Dining Room), 25 1/4"x18 1/4", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, N/A
    - 3/10/1908-3/14/1908, Order Number 2047, 1824/4 (Folder 44)
      # 1-Panel -A- Basement, Iron Lined Wood Box, 14"x15 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Panel -A- Cellar, 10 1/2"x12", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
      #1-3/10/1908 #2-3/14/1908
    - 3/14/1908, Order Number 2047, 1824/8 (Folder 44)
      Panel -A- Cellar, Iron Lined Wood Box, 10 1/2"x12", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
    - 8/13/1985, A2 (Folder 45-46)
      Electrical and Finished Plans, Electric Plan, Finished Plan, Legend on Right Side, # 1-36 1/4"x24 1/4", Sepia Tone, # 2-36 1/4"x24", Sepia Tone, # 3-36"x24", Vellum, (Copy of # 4), # 4-36"x24", Vellum, # 5-36 1/8"x24", Paper (Tan Paper and Blue Ink), # 6-36 3/8"x24 1/4", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 7-36 1/2"x24 3/4", Paper (White Paper and Blue Ink), # 8-36 1/4"x24 3/4", Paper (Tan Paper and Blue Ink), # 9-36 3/4"x24 3/4", Paper (Tan Paper and Blue Ink), Architects, Bryan O'Rourke and Alan Orenbuch
    - undated (5/24/1983), E-1 (Rolled with Drawing M-1-M-9) (Folder 47)
      Electric-Cellar Floor Plan, Electric-Basement Floor Plan, Electric Riser Diagram, Power Panel PP. 2 and PP. 3 Schedule, Notes on the Left Side, 49 1/2"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects-Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 11/1/1985, No Number Listed (Folder 48)
      Apartment Rewiring-Basement, Notes on Bottom of the Page # 1-36 1/8"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 2-36 1/4"x24 5/8", Paper, Blue Ink, # 3-36 1/2"x24 5/8", Paper, Blue Ink, # 4-36 1/8"x23", Paper, White Paper with Black Ink, Architects, Lowy and Donnath Electric
    - undated (11/1985), No Number Listed (Folder 49)
      AS-Built Drawings-Alternations to Basement Apartment, # 136 1/8"x24", Paper, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, 1985 Electrical Finish Plans, 36 1/4'x24 3/4", Paper (Blue Ink), # 3-Written on the Front in Pen, 1985 Electric and Finish Plans, 36 1/4"x24 3/4", Paper (Blue Ink), # 4-36 1/8"x24 1/8", Paper, Architects, N/A
- First Floor, 1907-1983; 3
  - Building/Floor Plans, 3.1
    - 1981 April 17, 2 NY 33 (Folder 50)
      Ground Floor Plan, 41 5/8"x22, Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, Revised 2/4/1908; 103 NY 33 (Folder 50)
      First Story Plan, Second Story Plan, Mezzanine Story Plan (In Second), # 1-42"x32 1/4", Linen, # 2-41 3/4"x32 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-42"x32 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-41 1/8"x32 1/2", Paper (Blue Ink), # 5-42 3/4"x32 3/4", Polyester Paper, # 6-21 1/2"x16 3/4", Paper (Photocopier Paper), Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 6/15/1908-7/11/1908, 1109 (office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 55 -Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy #) (Folder 51)
      Plan of the Fire Place Openings in Different Rooms, Dining Room, Music Room, Library, Entrance Hall, Reception Room, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Mantel Facing and Hearth, Chamber # 2 1908, 34 7/8"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue, # 2-Written on the Back with Pencil, Traitel's Drawing of Fire Place Opening in Different Rooms, 34 5/8"x14 3/8", A Small Piece was Removed @ 1 1/4"x9 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      #1-6/15/1908, Revised 7/11/1908 #2-6/15/1908
    - Reception Room
      - 2/5/1908, 326 NY 33 (Folder 52)
        Plan, Reception Room, Half of the Floor, Half of the Ceiling, General Notes on the Right Side, # 1-34 1/2"x20", Tracing Paper, # 2-34 1/2"x19 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 327 NY 33 (Folder 52)
        West Elevation, Reception Room, # 1-29 7/8"x17 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 "x17 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 328 NY 33 (Folder 52)